appliedi.net 2019-12-02

# Applied Innovations Privacy Policy

Effective Date: March 15th, 2014

This Privacy Policy discusses how Applied Innovations Corp. (Appliedi.net) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from our customers, visitors to our websites, individuals who contact us and visitors to our customers’ websites (all: Users). Please review our Privacy Policy in conjunction with our Acceptable Use Policy (AUP) and your contract with us. The terms of this Privacy Policy are in addition to the terms of our AUP and our contract. We offer products and services that are provided by third parties (Third Party Products). These Third Party Products may collect and use information in ways that differ from those set out in this Privacy Policy. Please contact us if you would like a list of these third parties. We have no responsibility for how these third parties treat your information; however, if we have access to their privacy policies, we will provide them to you on your request. We collect information from Users in many ways. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide Users with an understanding of what types of information we collect, how we treat it, and choices they may have related to this information. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this policy, other than necessary to remedy typographical errors, will be announced on our home page, as well as in email to the primary address you have on file with us. If you have a question about how a certain type of information is handled, please e-mail us at: support@appliedi.net.  
We participate in the U.S. / EU and U.S. / Swiss Safe Harbor programs

For data subject to the European Union’s Data Protection Directive, AppliedI has certified that it complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. For data subject to Switzerland’s Federal Act on Data Protection, AppliedI.net has certified it complies with the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. To learn more about the Safe Harbor programs, and to view Applied.net’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. AppliedI.net complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Appliedi.net has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Appliedi.net’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/. This Policy covers sites administered by Appliedi.net on behalf of customers and all information held by Appliedi.net and processed using systems associated with these sites. This Policy and Appliedi.net’s privacy practices have been reviewed by eTrust, and have been awarded eTrust’s “PrivacyTrust Seal.” In addition, Appliedi.net’s privacy practices and this Policy comply with eTrust’s program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of personal information. eTrust’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, or complaints about the way information is handled under it, please contact Appliedi.net first at 855.2.THECLOUD or by mail at 1001 Yamato Road Suite 300W Boca Raton, FL 33431.

**1\. Information That We Collect**  
Customer Record – When users become customers they provide us with their address, email, phone number, and credit card. Users may also provide us with their fax number and company affiliation (together “Customer Record”).

Inquiries – When Users contact us we may ask for information that allows us to contact them, validate the seriousness of their inquiry and request specific information related to the reason they have contacted us (User Inquiry Information). Appliedi.net does not intentionally collect data from persons under 13 years of age.

Surveys – Users may be offered the opportunity to respond to surveys, questionnaires and other requests for information (Survey Information). The types of data that Users provide to us is set out in the survey request.

Statistical Information – All of our servers collect statistical information such as users’ IP addresses, dates users visit, computers users are using, and operating system, among other data (Statistical Information).

Cookies – Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small data files that are placed automatically on a customer’s computer by our computers. These data files are read by our computer to determine whether you have visited our site before, how often, the length of time and which pages you view. The equipment we use to provide services to users may also place cookies on their computers.

Tracking Software – We may use software designed to track responses to our advertisements, other promotional activity as well as a user’s movement through our site, as well as external sites (Tracking Software). Tracking Software includes software such as web beacons and software used by our advertising partners. Tracking Software may be used by us in conjunction with marketing information we collect about you, or you provide to the Tracking Software provider. If this is the case, Tracking Software may identify you personally.

Payment Information - Payment information is processed by a third party processing service. The processing service maintains this data in an encrypted format. This data is not accessible on our systems.

**2\. How We Use Information That We Collect**  
Subpoenas and Other Demands for Information – Appliedi.net is required to comply with demands for information as dictated by state and Federal law. Examples of these demands include subpoenas, warrants, and civil discovery demands. Information covered by our Privacy Policy may be disclosed following such a request if we determine, in our sole discretion, that such a disclosure is necessary or required. We may also disclose this information if it is necessary or required to protect our interests, the interests of our customers, or in connection with the sale of our business.

Customer Record – We use the Customer Record to identify Users personally. It is used throughout our business to provide services to Users. Information in your Customer Record will only be shared with third parties if it is necessary to provide Third Party products to you. However, information in the Customer Record related to payments, such as a User’s credit card number, is only used to ensure we receive payment for services rendered. Credit card information is protected by SSL technology.

Customer Inquiries – We use Customer Inquiry Information to identify Users personally. It is used throughout our business to provide services to Users. Customer Inquiry Information is shared with third parties in the following circumstances: to identify and fix problems with services we provide when we are not capable of doing so ourselves.

Survey Information – We use Survey Information to identify Users personally. We use it throughout our business to market new products and services to Users. Survey Information is not shared with third parties in ways that identify Users personally. To the extent we share Survey Information with third parties, it is done in aggregate.

Statistical Information – We do not use Statistical Information to identify Users personally. We use statistical information to operate our hardware and software, diagnose problems and administer our website. We may use aggregate information to modify the products and services we offer based on who is visiting our website, and what they are purchasing.

Cookies – We may use Cookies to identify Users personally. We use the information provided by cookies to change the way our website looks to Users; to keep Users logged in to certain areas of the website; to ensure continued connection to the Equipment; and to collect demographic data about where Users go on our website and how they behave. Cookies used by our Equipment are used to track and log activities on the Equipment and our Network for security, network maintenance and other related activities.

Tracking Software – We use the information provided by Tracking Software to determine the effectiveness of our marketing programs; improve the functionality of our website; collect demographic data about where Users go on our website and how they behave; and to market to you directly, to the extent the Tracking Software contains personally identifiable information.

Deletion and Preservation of Information – Information covered by this Policy may be deleted upon a customer’s request. The Company may keep information covered by this Policy for a period of six months from the date of Customer’s termination of their relationship with Appliedi.net, or as required by law.

Changing and Correcting Information - If a customer wishes to access and/or update the information Appliedi.net has collected, the customer may either login to our website or client systems and view and change its information. If a customer would like a list of systems related to its account, this can also be obtained by contacting our accounting team. By request, Appliedi.net will delete all personally identifiable information from internal systems. All information would pass over to the new company in the event of a merger. In the event of bankruptcy, all information will be destroyed.

**3\. Data Retention And Security**  
We keep the information covered by this Privacy Policy indefinitely. Information collected from our website is protected by SSL 128 bit encryption technology during transmission. Information kept by us in our business is protected using industry standard security measures. Our employees are required to keep information covered by this Privacy Policy confidential – unless disclosure is authorized in this Privacy Policy, or by Users. No means of communication or information transmission or storage is totally secure. Because of this, we are not responsible for loss corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of information covered by this Privacy Policy, or for any resulting damages, including unauthorized acquisition and use.

**4\. Contact Information**  
Applied Innovations, Corp.  
1001 Yamato Road Suite 300W  
Boca Raton, FL 33431  
Phone: 855.2.THECLOUD  
Fax: 561.423.0390  
Email: info@appliedi.net
